

moshe.sh797@gmail.com

Moshe Shemen 053-5300261

Holon

## Education

- B.sc Electronics and Engineering
  2020-2024 Holon Institute of Technology
  certificate in embedded.
  Gpa: 85
- Electronic Practical Engineering
  2015- 2017 ORT Singalovski
  Gpa: 95
- Full matriculation
  2012- 2015 ORT Holon
  certificate in electronics and computers.

## Software

- C#
- VHDL
- Python
- Arduino
- MATLAB
- Linux
- Altium designer















ORT Singalovski | Electronic Practical Engineering **First class honors** 

## Moshe Shemen

# B.sc Electronics and Computer Engineer

## **Personal Summary**

I'm an Electronics and Computer Engineer specializing in embedded systems, with a passion for crafting electronic projects from a young age. I utilize Python, C++, Arduino, PCB builder, OpenCV, AI tools, and machine learning to bring my ideas to life.

My Projects: 🔘 My Github

## **Work Experience**

#### Quality inspector and integrator of thermal

Elop - Elbit Systems

2020- present

- Implementation of complex tests which combines electro-optics and electronics in the production line.
- Examining the reliability and functionality of a system during extreme Environmental Stress (ESS).
- Conducting Acceptance Test Procedure (ATP) which includes scope and laser beam analysis.
- Definition and establishment of electro-optical setups in cooperation with engineering entities.
- (System engineering / electronics / physics etc.), analysis of results and findings.
- Conducting system level troubleshooting and Fault verification.
- Familiarity with product life management (PLM), Bill of Materials (BOM), Engineering Change Proposal. (ECP).
- Writing programs in C# and Python to improve system quality.

#### Unit 8200, Intelligence corps

Military Service

2017-2020

- Full military service in a technical section in the field of extracting intelligence from a platform.
- Development and maintenance of a receive system in the platform and transfer of information to the user
- Solving hardware and software faults at the component replacement level based on reading electrical sketches.
- Writing programs in C# and VHDL to improve system quality.

## Languages

**Hebrew** Native

English full professional proficiency